Jai Hind friends, welcome to the new information video.
Friends, today in this video we
will talk about
which
profiles can you get a job in ICICI Bank if you are a fresher because if you
join a brand like ICICI Bank as a fresher, then your
future is very bright. So friends, first of all,
before starting the video, if you are
new to our channel then definitely like or subscribe
because I keep bringing all the updates related to banking finance on my channel
because if you are a fresher and are
looking for a job then this channel is best for you.
Let's start the video, so
friends, if you are a fresher and
want to make a career in banking and you do not have any
banking experience, then there are
four-five such profiles in ICICI Bank in which
you can easily enter. To
join a brand like ICICI Bank, if
you are a normal graduate then you
can join it. There is no need for any post-graduate or
any technical degree. Even if
you do not have a technical degree,
you can join the job. I will
take you through the career of ICICI Bank and what are the
positions in it and  What are the job
profiles? We will discuss everything. So,
this profile is
for every vertical. It is not that it is only
for sales because
in the banking industry,
these are the rumors everywhere in the market today. We get a lot of
comments that there is only sales, sales, sales, sales,
not a sales profile. There are
many types of profiles in the banking sector. There is
retail branch banking,
corporate banking, loan segment,
collection department, audit, that is, of
every type. Because it is banking, then
ICICI Bank has all kinds of services. So,
within this, you are not just a sales profile. It
depends on the bank's requirement at that time
and which
profile you are given.
Apart from this, many of my brothers and sisters get
messages that they only have
sales profiles and are leaving their jobs. So, for
this thing, first of all, let me tell you
that if you
want to make a career in the banking sector, then you should already
set a goal in your life
that I want to work in this sector, then you will be
able to do better in it and your career will be
bright.  So let me take you to the
IC Bank careers website and
show you
what jobs you can get as a fresher
and what
criteria are required to enter. So let's go.
I've opened the IC Bank careers
website. There are
always openings for freshers.
You can enter IC Bank as a fresher. First, look at the
Post Graduate Program in
Relationship Management. This Post
Graduate Program in Relationship Management is only
for sales profiles. By doing a
normal graduate course, it's a
short-duration course. It's a 20-
day course. You
can directly enter the bank after doing one course. You do
n't need any technical knowledge or a technical degree. It's a very easy process.
If you go to it, go to the About the More
Program section and get a complete brief.
You can see what's
included and how you can enter it. If you
want, you can get employed within a month.
If you are looking for a job
immediately, you can enroll
in this program by undergoing 20-21 days of
training.
Another program is the
ICICI Bank PO program, which is conducted
through IC Manipal. It's a
full one-year program, with
four months of classroom training,
followed by an internship, then an OGT.
After one year, you're offered the position of
Deputy Manager.
In IC Bank, you can get an initial package of ₹55 lakh
as a fresher.
This is a very good job. If you
look at the postgraduate program,
you can get a package of ₹2.5 to 3 lakh,
and as a fresher, you can
get a job within 20 to 21 days. This is a very
easy process. If you need a job,
you can easily apply.
Furthermore, ICICI Bank has a
large number of vacancies for phone banking officers.
Phone banking officers provide knowledge
for customer services.  The
level will be very high.
If you
go for this profile in the banking sector, then complete
training is given to you. What will happen from this is that
if you work in this vertical for even some time, then
you will have complete knowledge of the product. The
first thing I will tell you about the banking industry is that
if we look at this industry, then it
is the fastest growing industry in India. If you become an
associate with any bank and
work for a few days, and gain knowledge, then
you
can easily get your salary growth by switching to other banks, NBFCs, or insurance companies. And
you will see where you will take your profile within 5 to 7 years or 10 years.
You
cannot even imagine, but you will have to work in it.
After this, see there is campus
requirement also within this. If you have
already decided that
you want to go into the banking industry, then
if you are going to college for MBA, then
you can see whether there is
placement of ICICI Bank there or not
because the place from where ICICI Bank picks
its employees is from colleges.
Through MBA, his career is very bright, there is
also a process of promotion in one to two years, the
salary is very high, so
in whichever college you are going for intermediate, you are
taking admission for MBA or graduation, then
you can find out whether there is a
placement process with ICB
or not, you can also search the past track record,
so all this and
you will also get the name of the college inside it,
you can check everything by going to about, so
these are four types of
programs that ICB provides for freshers,
in which you can also get
intermediate and you can start your career,
so
you can easily make your career by getting intermediate with the largest bank in India,
and if you keep your goal right in life, then
your career is very bright
because in a brand like ICB, there
is a lot of learning for you and the
banking sector is growing a lot, so
you can make your career like this, so
friends, I hope this video
is very informative, like a
Please subscribe, thank you very much